{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "______.",
      "a": "Whom did you talk to?",
      "b": "To who did you talk?",
      "c": "Whom did you talk?",
      "d": "Who did you talk?",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Whom: We use whom to ask which person receives an action \n+ \"whom\" should be used as objects of prepositions, these prepositions can stand before \"whom\" or after the main Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ house is this? Who owns it?",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "Who",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ house is that by the river?' 'Mr Smith's.'",
      "a": "Which",
      "b": "Whose",
      "c": "Whom",
      "d": "What",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can see them, but ________ is your brother?",
      "a": "whose",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "which one",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- which one: use to stress the right thing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ of these two hotels is the most expensive?",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "What",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "That",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ writes these jokes?",
      "a": "Whom",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "What",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is\n+ Ask for Subject: Who + Verb\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who ________ the glass?' 'Johnny did.'",
      "a": "did break",
      "b": "broken",
      "c": "broke",
      "d": "has broke",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is \n+ Ask for Subject: Who + Verb ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose car _______ down?",
      "a": "did it break",
      "b": "break",
      "c": "did break",
      "d": "broke",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Ask for subject: Whose + Noun + Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ of these girls is the prettiest?",
      "a": "Whom",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "Who",
      "d": "Whose",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I found a wallet.' '________ is it?'",
      "a": "Which",
      "b": "Whose",
      "c": "What",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}